androidbiits.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Android Biits

At Androidbiits.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy page depicts the types of personal information is received and collected by Androidbiits.com and how it is used.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Androidbiits.com does use cookies to save information about visitors preferences, save user-specific information on which web pages the visitor visit, modify Web page content based on visitors web browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their web browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Androidbiits.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to Androidbiits.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at this URL: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

You should note that the third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Androidbiits.com send directly to your web browsers. They obtain your IP address automatically when this occurs. Other technologies (such as Web Beacons, cookies, or JavaScript) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to determine the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Androidbiits.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You can consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Androidbiits.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and it is not possible to control the activities of these advertisers.

If you want to disable cookies, then you can do so through your individual web browser options. You can obtain more information about cookie management with specific web browsers at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you have any questions or require any more information about our privacy policy, then you can contact us.
